<cockatrice_carddatabase version="4">
  <sets>
    <set>
      <name>DM23-SP1</name>
      <longname>DM23-SP1</longname>
      <settype>DM23-SP1</settype>
      <releasedate>2023-11-05</releasedate>
    </set>
  </sets>
  <cards>
    <card>
      <name>Perfect Darkness</name>
      <text>
■ You may cast this spell from your graveyard, If you do, after casting, put it on the bottom of your deck instead. 
■  Choose 2 of the following. ''(You may choose the same one twice.)''
:► Your opponent chooses a card in their hand and discards it.
:► Put a darkness creature that costs 4 or less or darkness aura that costs 4 or less from your graveyard into the battle zone. 
:► Choose one of your opponent's creatures. That creature gets -4000 power until the End Step
  </text>
      <prop>
        <maintype>Spell</maintype>
        <type></type>
        <manacost>5</manacost>
        <colors>Darkness</colors>
        <pt></pt>
      </prop>
      <set num="DM23-SP1-5">DM23-SP1</set>
      <related></related>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Fork %3D Fock</name>
      <text>
■ When you put this creature, you may put the top 3 cards of your deck into your graveyard. If you do, you may return an Abyss from your graveyard to your hand.
  </text>
      <prop>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <type>Abyss Royale</type>
        <manacost>3</manacost>
        <colors>Darkness</colors>
        <pt>4000</pt>
      </prop>
      <set num="DM23-SP1-15">DM23-SP1</set>
      <related></related>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Abyssbell %3D Jashin Emperor</name>
      <text>
■ Blocker
■ Double Breaker
■ Your Abyss creatures in your graveyard get "Abyss Rush". ''(You may summon a creature that has "Abyss Rush" from your graveyard. If you do, that creature can attack players this turn and is put on the bottom of your deck at the End Step
■ When this creature would leave, you may discard 2 cards from your hand instead.
■ Your creatures in your graveyard cost 2 less to summon. They can't cost 0 or less.
  </text>
      <prop>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <type>Abyss Royale</type>
        <manacost>4</manacost>
        <colors>Darkness</colors>
        <pt>7000</pt>
      </prop>
      <set num="DM23-SP1-2">DM23-SP1</set>
      <related></related>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Torch %3D Totorot, Evil Light</name>
      <text>
■ Shield Trigger
■ Blocker
■ When you put this creature, your opponent chooses one of their creatures that has the lowest power and destroys it.
■ '''Civil Count 3''': When you put this creature, if you have a total of 3 or more darkness creatures and/or darkness tamaseeds, your opponent chooses one of their creatures that has the highest power and destroys it.
■ When this creature attacks, destroy this creature after the attack.
  </text>
      <prop>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <type>Abyss Royale</type>
        <manacost>7</manacost>
        <colors>Darkness</colors>
        <pt>5000</pt>
      </prop>
      <set num="DM23-SP1-7">DM23-SP1</set>
      <related></related>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Belle %3D Gelelle</name>
      <text>
■ Abyss Rush
■ When you put this creature, put the top 2 cards of your deck into your graveyard.
  </text>
      <prop>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <type>Abyss Royale</type>
        <manacost>2</manacost>
        <colors>Darkness</colors>
        <pt>1000</pt>
      </prop>
      <set num="DM23-SP1-16">DM23-SP1</set>
      <related></related>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Bauwauja, Abyssal Three Roar</name>
      <text>
■ When you put this tamaseed, you may put the top 4 cards of your deck into your graveyard.
■ If you don't have a total of 4 or more darkness creatures and/or darkness tamaseeds, this tamaseed isn't treated as a creature in the battle zone.
■ Blocker
■ Triple Breaker
■ Whenever this creature attacks, destroy one of your opponent's creatures.
■ During your turn, this tamaseed can't leave except by being destroyed.
  </text>
      <prop>
        <maintype>Tamaseed / Creature</maintype>
        <type>Abyss Royale/ACE</type>
        <manacost>4</manacost>
        <colors>Darkness</colors>
        <pt>13000</pt>
      </prop>
      <set num="DM23-SP1-6">DM23-SP1</set>
      <related></related>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Hamma %3D Dhamma</name>
      <text>
■ Shield Trigger
■ When you put this creature, you may put the top 3 cards of your deck into your graveyard. Then choose one of your opponent's creatures that costs less than the number of cards in your graveyard and destroy it.
  </text>
      <prop>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <type>Abyss Royale</type>
        <manacost>4</manacost>
        <colors>Darkness</colors>
        <pt>2000</pt>
      </prop>
      <set num="DM23-SP1-14">DM23-SP1</set>
      <related></related>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Madan %3D Row, Abyssal Furnace</name>
      <text>
■ Slayer
■ When you put this creature, look at your opponent's hand and discard a creature from it. 
■ '''Civil Count 3''': Whenever this creature attacks, if you have a total of 3 or more darkness creatures and/or darkness tamaseeds, you may choose a card in your opponent's graveyard. You may use one of that card's "when you put" abilities. Then your opponent puts that card on the bottom of their deck.
  </text>
      <prop>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <type>Abyss Royale</type>
        <manacost>4</manacost>
        <colors>Darkness</colors>
        <pt>4000</pt>
      </prop>
      <set num="DM23-SP1-4">DM23-SP1</set>
      <related></related>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Broom %3D Proof</name>
      <text>
■ When you put this creature, put the top card of your deck into your graveyard. 
■ During your opponent's turn, whenever your opponent puts a creature in any way except by summoning, destroy that creature.
  </text>
      <prop>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <type>Abyss Royale</type>
        <manacost>2</manacost>
        <colors>Darkness</colors>
        <pt>3000</pt>
      </prop>
      <set num="DM23-SP1-10">DM23-SP1</set>
      <related></related>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Eido %3D Meido/"Do You Want to See the Abyss?"</name>
      <text>
■ Triple Breaker
■ When you put this creature, choose one of your opponent's creatures and destroy it.
■ Whenever this creature attacks, you may return a card from your graveyard to your hand.
=========================
■ Put the top 2 cards of your deck into your graveyard.
  </text>
      <prop>
        <maintype>Twinpact</maintype>
        <type>Abyss Royale/Invitation to the Abyss</type>
        <manacost>7</manacost>
        <colors>Darkness/Darkness</colors>
        <pt>12000</pt>
      </prop>
      <set num="DM23-SP1-9">DM23-SP1</set>
      <related></related>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Do:Norateppu</name>
      <text>
■ Slayer
■ Once per turn, your Abyss may cost 1 less to use. They can't cost 0 or less.
  </text>
      <prop>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <type>Noir Abyss</type>
        <manacost>2</manacost>
        <colors>Darkness</colors>
        <pt>1000</pt>
      </prop>
      <set num="DM23-SP1-17">DM23-SP1</set>
      <related></related>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
    </card>
    <card>
      <name>Do:Sumonma</name>
      <text>
■ Blocker
■ When you put this creature, choose one of the following.
:► You may put 4 cards in your graveyard on the bottom of your deck in any order. If you do, Abyss Mechraid 8. Mechraid
  </text>
      <prop>
        <maintype>Creature</maintype>
        <type>Noir Abyss</type>
        <manacost>5</manacost>
        <colors>Darkness</colors>
        <pt>3000</pt>
      </prop>
      <set num="DM23-SP1-12">DM23-SP1</set>
      <related></related>
      <tablerow>2</tablerow>
    </card>
  </cards>
</cockatrice_carddatabase>